the file. I have pulled both of the files into my Kali machine. Let me try to dump both
of the files. We are going to use a registry module and SAM, you need to do the SAM file.
And the next one for the system, they are you need to give a system. Let me collect the
as SAM and as system. So give me a sick, let me verify the command. Basically I have tried
a lot of techniques, you know, by pick cats, but it was not okay. So this could be an actual
command because anyway we are going to register doing registry based thing. And it could
be a SAM. So we can use it like the dash dash SAM and the SAM file and the system
was missing. But yeah, now it has hurt to properly. So you can see the hash of the users
here. Let me take the hash of the, this user. And let me go through the, crack station.
And so, okay, the password as an hash, sorry, the password, the password of the user
was a pass. And also, I have discovered one more method to dig an information, it is
secret dump.ty. So you can find out from this, this repo, just you can, you can search
it in Google like secret dump.ty, you can first you can download it once you, once you
download the secret dump, let's execute the secret dump like this. So Python 3 secret dump.ty.
So to install this, you need an impact library, you have to, you have to install the impact
library, then once you done, if you execute the secret dump.ty, it will be giving this
results, okay. So the Python 3 and secret dump.ty. So dash for a SAM and dash for system,
the system 5 and local, okay. So both of the methods, what, in our technique. So you
have to give it like this, okay. I just given one more parameter like dash test system that
was, that was an error. So you can give it like this, okay. So in this given information
like the control set, let's say, current control set 001 and these are some secrets, okay.
So let's, I hope you have a clear understanding about the dumping the credentials, see we
have used both of the commands. So one is a pipette registry SAM system and we have
dumped using a secret dump.ty like this, okay. These are the two commands we have, we have
used here. So hope, you have a clear understanding about the credential access techniques
and extracting the information from the, uh, Elsa and the SAM and system Hives. Okay.
So we'll hop off and we'll connect you guys in the next session. Thank you, bye.